Intelligent Workplace Training

Integrations

Theme  

Light Dark System

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last updated: June 17, 2024_
-----------------------------

The privacy of your data — and it is your data, not ours! — is a big deal to us. In this policy, we lay out: what data we collect and why; how your data is handled; and your rights to your data. We promise to never sell your data.

When we say "company", "we", "our, "us", "Cassava", "application", "bot", "service" or "services" in this document, we are referring to Cassavarose LLC.

When we say "platform" in this document, we are referring to your integrations wtih Cassava which includes Slack, Microsoft Teams, and Webex.

What we collect and why
=======================

Our guiding principle is to collect only what we need and that we will solely process this information to provide you with the service you signed up for.

We use a select number of trusted external service providers for certain service offerings. These service providers are carefully selected and meet high data protection, data privacy and security standards. We only share information with them that is required for the services offered.

Here’s what all this means in practice:

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Identity & Access
=================

When you register for an account with Cassava, we request access to your platform and identity via OAuth or via direct installation by means of the App directory. Your platform provides one or more tokens to facilitate this process.

As part of registration, we obtain the bare minimum information regarding your account to allow us to authenticate and authorize your use of Cassava. We collect your platform id, platform name, platform tokens, and scopes during authentication. During authorization we also collect your name, platform user id, user tokens, scopes, profile photo where available, as well as your locale and timezone when provided.

At any time you can invite members of your platform to collaborate on your Cassava Experiences, and in doing so we ask them to identify themselves by signing in to the platform. People outside your organization can also be invited to collaborate by providing a personal email address in exchange for a [Magic Link](https://auth0.com/blog/what-is-passwordless-authentication/) token.

The purpose of self identification in each case is so that we can authenticate and authorize your use of Cassava. We’ll never sell your personal information to third parties, and we won’t use your name or company in marketing statements without your permission.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Billing Information
===================

When you directly purchase a recurring subscription to Cassava on our platform, we ask for your credit card and other billing information, so that we can charge you for service, calculate taxes due, and send you invoices. We use [Stripe](https://stripe.com/privacy) as our payment processor and as such your credit card is passed directly to them from your browser and never goes through our servers. We store a record of the payment transaction, including the last 4 digits of the credit card number for account history, invoicing, and billing support.

Subscriptions which are purchased via our external partner platforms are managed therein.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Geolocation data
================

We maintian an audit record of all IP addresses during sign-ins for the purpose of checking for unauthorized activity. We keep this login data for as long as your account is active.

IP addresses are also logged each time a request is made by an authenticated user. This includes users who have explictly signed in as well as those for whom a cookie has been set. See the cookie section for more information.

We also log the IP address of anonymous user visits as a standard security policy to guard against bad actors.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Website Interactions
====================

We use Plausible Analytics, a GDPR, CCPA and cookie law compliant site analytics tool, to measure overall trends in the usage of our website. Plausible Analytics only collects aggregated information. No cookies are used for Analytics and no Personal Identifiable Information (PII) such as your IP address or browser user agent is stored. You are encouraged to view [Plausible Analytics Data Policy](https://plausible.io/data-policy) and learn more about their Do Not Track Policy and other privacy tenets.

As you build content on Cassava, you may upload attachments to your Experience. These attachments are uploaded directly to Amazon Web Services (AWS) and served from Amazon CloudFront. See the [AWS Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/?nc1=f_pr) for more information..

From time to time we may send transactional emails to those users who authenticate with an email address. In these instances we use Mailjet as our provider. See the [Mailjet Privacy Policy](https://www.mailjet.com/privacy-policy/) for more details. As an added measure of privacy we do not track email open and click events in Mailjet. These features are off.

We use CAPTCHA service as a means of spam protection on some of our forms. hCaptcha is a GDPR-compliant and privacy-friendly captcha. See the [hCaptcha Privacy Policy](https://www.hcaptcha.com/privacy) for full details.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Cookies
=======

When you sign into Cassava we store persistent first-party cookies in your browser for purpopses of authentication and authorization only. These cookies are removed when they expire or when you sign out of Cassava. To learn more about cookies, including how to view which cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://gocassava.com/We%20do%20not%20track%20people%20across%20their%20devices%20and%20across%20websites).

A cookie is set for Audience members who use email as their distribution channel and access the site to complete their Experience.

We also store a cookie when you leave a comment on the blog and select the **Remember me** option. This cookie remains in place until expiration.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Voluntary Correspondence
========================

When you write Cassava with a question or to ask for help, we keep that correspondence, including the email address, so that we have a history of past correspondences to reference if you reach out in the future.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Information we do not collect
=============================

We don’t collect any characteristics of protected classifications including age, race, gender, religion, sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, or physical and mental abilities or disabilities.

We also do not collect any biometric data. We show whatever profile photo you have provided in your platform and do not extract any information from it.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

When we access or share your information
========================================

Our default practice is to not access your information. The only times we’ll ever access or share your info are:

**To help you troubleshoot or squash a software bug which impacts your use of Cassava**. When you reach out to us for assistance in this matter you implicitly grant us the right to review your account to support debugging the issue.

**To investigate, prevent, or take action regarding restricted uses**. Accessing a customer’s account when investigating potential abuse is a measure of last resort. We have an obligation to protect the privacy and safety of both our customers and the people reporting issues to us. We do our best to balance those responsibilities throughout the process. If we do discover you are using our products for a restricted purpose, we will report the incident to the appropriate authorities.

**To support coaching facilitations**. We share limited details of your organization's members with coaches. This allows the coach to identify audience participants. Cassava is the trusted middleman in this relationship between coach and client, and we never share sensitive information with either party, such as access tokens. We publish the content to your organization on behalf of the coach.

**When required under applicable law**. Cassavarose LLC is a US company.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Your rights with respect to your information
============================================

At Cassava, we apply the same data rights to all customers, regardless of their location. Currently some of the most privacy-forward regulations in place are the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) in the US. Cassava recognizes all of the rights granted in these regulations, except as limited by applicable law. These rights include:

**Right to Know.** You have the right to know what personal information is collected, used, shared or sold. We outline both the categories and specific bits of data we collect, as well as how they are used, in this privacy policy.

**Right of Access.** This includes your right to access the personal information we gather about you, and your right to obtain information about the sharing, storage, security and processing of that information.

**Right to Correction.** You have the right to request correction of your personal information.

**Right to Erasure / “To be Forgotten”.** This is your right to request, subject to certain limitations under applicable law, that your personal information be erased from our possession and, by extension, all of our service providers. Fulfillment of some data deletion requests may prevent you from using Casava services because our applications may then no longer work. In such cases, a data deletion request may result in closing your account.

**Right to Complain.** You have the right to make a complaint regarding our handling of your personal information with the appropriate supervisory authority. To identify your specific authority or find out more about this right, EU individuals should go to [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en).

**Right to Restrict Processing.** This is your right to request restriction of how and why your personal information is used or processed, including opting out of sale of personal information. (Again: we never will sell your personal data.)

**Right to Object.** You have the right, in certain situations, to object to how or why your personal information is processed.

**Right to Portability.** You have the right to receive the personal information we have about you and the right to transmit it to another party.

**Right to not be subject to Automated Decision-Making.** You have the right to object and prevent any decision that could have a legal, or similarly significant, effect on you from being made solely based on automated processes. This right is limited, however, if the decision is necessary for performance of any contract between you and us, is allowed by applicable law, or is based on your explicit consent.

**Right to Non-Discrimination.** This right stems from the CCPA. We do not and will not charge you a different amount to use our products, offer you different discounts, or give you a lower level of customer service because you have exercised your data privacy rights. However, the exercise of certain rights (such as the right “to be forgotten”) may, by virtue of your exercising those rights, prevent you from using our Services.

If you have questions about exercising these rights or need assistance, please contact us at privacy@gocassava.com. For requests to delete personal information or know what personal information has been collected, we will first verify your identity using a combination of at least two pieces of information already collected. If an authorized agent is corresponding on your behalf, we will first need written consent with a signature from the account holder before proceeding.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

How we secure your data
=======================

All data is encrypted via [SSL/TLS](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security) when transmitted to your browser from our servers hosted on Digital Ocean.

Any OAuth tokens we received from you that are designated for storage in our database are first encrypted.

All live data in our database clusters is encrypted at rest with LUKS (Linux Unified Key Setup) and in transit with SSL. Data held in routine backups are also encrypted.

Furthermore, our database modeling architecture uses a Multitenant strategy to enforce the isolation of data within each account.

See [Digital Ocean Privacy Policy](https://www.digitalocean.com/legal/privacy-policy/) for more information.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

What happens when you delete data in your account
=================================================

Unless otherwise stated, anything you delete in your Cassava Experiences is permanent and irreversible. We prompt you to confirm your intention before performing costly deletions as a measure of precaution.

We also delete your data after an account is closed.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Location of site and data
=========================

Cassava operates in the United States and as such the primary data you share with us is stored on servers provided by Digitial Ocean in the United States. Refer to the privacy policies of our third party providers for the location and storage of data.

If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, **please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to and stored in the United States**. By using our Site, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Data Retention
==============

We will retain your information as long as your account is active, as necessary to provide you with the services, or as otherwise outlined in this policy.

We will also retain and use this information as necessary for the purposes set out in this policy and to the extent required to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and protect Cassavarose LLC's legal rights.

You can choose to delete your Cassava account at any time by making a request to Customer Support at support@gocassava.com. We will review the request and direct you to the steps to proceed. Upon approval, we will permanently delete all your data in our live database when you delete your account. Data in our backups may persist until those backups are purged.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Changes & questions
===================

We may update this policy as needed to comply with relevant regulations and reflect any new practices. Whenever we make a significant change to our policies, we will also announce them on our [company blog](https://gocassava.com/blog) and/or the dashboard.

Have any questions, comments, or concerns about this privacy policy, your data, or your rights with respect to your information? Please get in touch by emailing us at privacy@gocassava.com and we’ll be happy to answer them!

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

 Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. Donec sed odio dui. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.

Submit

Submit

v3.1.1.02d5198© 2024 Cassavarose LLC. All rights reserved

 [](https://gocassava.com/blog/three-fantastic-techniques-to-quickly-learn-anything)3 Fantastic Techniques to Quickly Learn Anything

 [](https://gocassava.com/blog/supercharge-creation-training-modules-mind-maps-cassava)Supercharge the Creation of Training Modules with Mind Maps and Cassava

 [](https://gocassava.com/blog/cassava-for-business-coaches)Maximize the Engagement, Adoption, and Retention of your Business Coaching Programs

Company

Overview

Contact
